I trust my president, but if the
я доверяю своему президенту но если б у
actions were not of course bad, then what
действиями не конечно плохо то что
happened is that it was necessary to
случилось такое что надо было
invade Ukraine, otherwise it began on
вторгнуться в украину а то началась 14
April 14, 2 days after the capture
апреля через 2 дня после захвата
of the Girkin Slavic police station, the
отделения полиции гиркина славянской
first day
первый день
I watch people from Russia ask
смотреть я у людей из россии спрашивают
how you feel about the war  well, if it’s
как вы относитесь к войне ну коли не
not that I don’t feel good about his childhood, that
то что его детство плохо отношусь то
is, you think that the
есть вы считаете что неправильно удастся
Russian troops will succeed wrong, we fly the
русские войска вышли мы флинну
world trusting our president, but because
мир доверяя своему президенту но из-за
of the hostilities they are of course bad, that
боевых действий они конечно плохо то
is, it turns out you just support
есть получается вы поддержите ли просто
this moral suffering
у вас моральное это острое страдания
because of  yes, of
из-за этого да
course, then practically all of us have
ну естественно тогда гибнут у нас у всех
relatives in Ukraine, and
практически из родственники на украине а
why do you support here is your motivation,
почему вы поддержите вот ваша мотивация
what
какая
brand to go like this, let’s say you
марка деваться такая допустим вы пришли
came, your stomach hurts to the doctor, the doctor says
у вас болит живот к врачу врач говорит
you have appendicitis, you need to have an
вас аппендицит необходимо сделать
operation, for my own reasons, I say
операцию я за своих соображений говорю
no, I won’t  make all the crisis will be from the
нет не буду сделать все кризис будет из
abode the stomach will pass did and died I
обители живот пройдет сделал и сдох я
apologize for such a french
извиняюсь за такой французский
doctor  I’m talking to a competent person, because at
врачу компетентному человеку поскольку в
first I also doubted
президенту я тоже поначалу сомневался в
his actions as a president, also competence
его действиях тоже компетенция
influences, perhaps even
воздействиях возможно даже в
opposition ones
оппозиционных
over time, after that I voted for him more than once
со временем я за него после не раз за
before that, I didn’t vote for him
него голосовал до этого не за него
everything, everything that he didn’t do as a
голосовал все-все чтобы он не делал в
result turned out to be the best
результате оказался то прям наилучшим
decision building moveable let's
решением здание подвижно давайте это за
move on from the allegory of a doctor because
перейдем от аллегории врача потому что
every doctor can be inept doctors
врачи всякий бывает есть врачи неумелые
and you will come he had the spirit
так и и тебе придет у него были духа ему
cut off his leg so let
отрезали отрезали ногу так что давайте
's explain what
вот объясните чем тогда
exactly Ukraine threatened Russia then or
конкретно украина угрожала россии или
that Russia invaded
что что россия сделала вторжение в
Ukraine
украину
to create everything with glory, since on the 14th
все славою по творить поскольку 14-го
year I actively observe all what
года активно наблюдаю все какие
different things and videos, very many from the
различные вещи и видео очень многие с
so-called gray zone here, for example, I’m
так называемую серой зоне тут примеру я
here on 2 today to read and on May 2, perhaps
тут на 2 сегодня читать и 2 мая возможно
some kind of anniversaries like 8 and
какая-то своеобразные годовщины как 8 и
8 machete seven years occurred in  Odessa
8 machete семь лет произошедшие в одессе
until
до
I watched streams directly and absolutely
я прямо стримы смотрел и совершенно
opposite things are not said by those who
противоположные вещи не говорят те кто
love their father and those  However, I
любят отец и тем не менее я
’m sure that HIV, which happened
уверен что и вич которые произошли вот
eight years ago, is extremely wrong, but
восемь лет назад крайне неправильны но
these are also anti-Maidan in many ways,
эти по многим вещам также антимайдан
which, in fact, have low-low
который которого фактически низко-низко
results, people guys just
результатов людей парней просто куда-то
disappeared somewhere who went with Crimea, then
исчезла которые ехали с крым потом
went back to the heart, not in Kherson, to
поехали обратно в сердце не в херсоне в
in this Mariupol on May 9, what happened in
этом мариуполе в 9 мая что происходило в
Kharkov, what happened there,
харькова что происходило там
let's look, assuming a series,
давайте смотреть допустив череда
let's say in the fourteenth year there was
допустим в четырнадцатом году было
something bad in Ukraine, so
что-то плохое в украине так вот а
on February 24,
24 февраля
2022, what happened such that it
2022 года что случилось такое что надо
was necessary to invade Ukraine
было вторгнуться в украину
explains well February 21, 21 on the very
хорошо объясняет 21 21 февраля на самом
in fact, the guys who actually
деле ребята которая собственно
[music]
[музыка]
they say that from the 18th the shelling began to
они говорят что с 18 числа начали уже
increase specifically on the positions of the
нарастать обстрелы конкретно по позициям
2nd 4th 21st, in general, the horror of some kind of god
2 4 21 числа вообще ужас какой-то бог
life is full, but accordingly,
жизнь полная но соответственно пришлось
these formations had to be recognized as
признать эти образования как
an independent state
самостоятельно государственном
formation, as it is visible and somehow there
образовании как виден и как-то так там
is called a cooperation agreement and the
называется договор о сотрудничестве ну и
commonwealth there had to help the DPR
содружества там сюда пришлось помочь днр
and LPR, otherwise I had to  Putin was for the
и лнр а то я до этого путин был за
implementation of the Minsk agreements, as far
исполнение минских соглашений насколько
as I understand, what he understands read them for a long time
это понимаю то что понимает давно их
-2, more precisely, they were logical and
читал -2 точнее они были логичными и
really normal mixes for
правде нормальными миксы для пройдут уже
the DPR and LPR would have been quite for themselves, the
было бы вполне себе днр и лнр оставались
only thing they were allowed to do
украине единственное что им разрешено
was to enter Russian as the state language
было в русский язык как государственный
from the window and  they don’t have their own police there for some time,
от окна и там нет на некоторое время
but
своей милицию держать а так экономически
it was fully trained economically here,
сюда это полностью тренировалась тем не
however, Ukrainian would also be a sufficient
менее украинский был бы тоже достаточно
language and be sure to look at me,
языком и обязательно посмотри вам во мне
it doesn’t seem to you that the whole conflict
кажется вам не кажется что весь конфликт
in the Donbass started from the
на донбассе и так начался из
Russian special services and mercenaries, so from
российских спецслужб и наемников так с
what  from what date did it start,
какого с какого числа начали началась а
and from what date did the
то из какого числа начались боевые
hostilities in the Donbass
действия на донбассе
began, the guys who
боевые действия ребята которые там
did there after the Maidan before being on their
сделали после майдана до будучи ноги
feet agreed, practically Yanukovych was the
были согласны практически янукович был
president so much, although his soldiers were
президентом настолько хотя его солдаты
not offended for him, they voted for a
не был обижен за него голосовали не
few phrases, for example, and there are
нескольких фраз ли например и есть есть
people call for Biden, and someone calls for this
люди зовут за байдена а кто-то за этого
for Trump, so  this is an internal
за трампа так вот это внутренний
political issue, but look, on
политический вопрос так но смотрите 12
April 12, 2014,
апреля 2014 года произошел захват
the police station in the city of Slavyansk was seized
отделение полиции в городе славянск
by Russian militants,
российскими боевиками а
otherwise you can look, you can google it, otherwise it
то смотрите можете нагуглить а то
started on April 14, 2 days after the
началась 14 апреля через 2 дня после
capture of the police station, girkin of their
захвата отделения полиции гиркин их
Slavic
славянской
came, let's now google it and
пришел давайте вот сейчас вы нагуглить и
so
так
came flexible  On April 12, you can
пришел гибким 12 апреля можете
shoot the Slavic capture, let's let
пострелять захват славянские давайте
us determine, after all, from us, not the
чтобы мы определили все-таки от у нас не
first person says I specifically
первый человек говорит я специально
checked this so as not to deceive
проверял это так чтобы не обманывать
people Girkin came on the 12th from her
людей гиркин пришел 12-го числа от она
part two days later from his own
часть через два дня от собственного
capture of the police department
захват отделение полиции
robbery and over civilians  citizens and
разбой и над мирными гражданами так и
led to the fact that they
привело к тому что
announced it, otherwise it was a pity that they
огласили а то
squeezed it
жалко сжал
in them
в их жалко да
, it’s a pity, it’s a pity, so then the
жалко так то вот
Russians are just dry and the facts of the
россиян она просто сухим и фактами
pacino eat the Russian date, that is, he
пачино ешь русского дата то есть он его
beat him there,
там побил
hammered bombas, and so on there Ukrainians
долбили bombas и так далее там украинцы
there 6 to 1000.
там 6 до 1000 . а
otherwise it started 14 quit not 2014 lesson 2
то так началась 14 quit не 2014 урок 2
days from this Russian militants pit the
дня от этого российские боевики пит
village of Girkin protective Slavyansk
деревне ством гиркина защитных славянск
and bought this tour saw me whips and
и закупил этом туре видел меня плети и
when and sad embarrassment over our peaceful
когда и печали смущения над мирным наш
conservation base from and
консервацией базу от и
out and start me not not but it was
вон и начинать мне не не а то было
before  otherwise it was less than Q and you are
раньше а то было меньше q и ты их
not listening to everyone with a rag to choke
слушаешь не каждого тряпочкой подавиться
inside to join and in them the
внутри влиться бачить и в них пропадают
arguments are still in our ear to K to K to K to K to
аргументы еще у нас ухо к к к к к к к к
I ask these
я задаю эти к этому
all the fact that the Rockets
всем тем что кажи там висим rocket
bombed Donbass tells this way there.
бомбили донбасс это трава рассказывает
even in the donbas soon dota docker
еще на донбассе бы вскоре dota докер
russia would look like these terrorist
россия выглядела этих террористических
groups it's the manager of girkin did not enter the
групп it's управдом гиркина не зашли
first places did not
первые места не закупили
buy mergies of the place so on I come in I saw
мергии места так на я заходите видел
greenhouses so in istanbul and its axis is such
теплицы так in istanbul и свою ось такие
there terrorists on a pirate so it was
там террористы на пиратке так и
suggested there it sold both sides of the
внушалось там его продал обе стороны
cabin like this  mayhem here is all the sheep and the
салона такой беспредел вот всех овца и
moose patch
патча лось